Oh Youth truly is wasted on the young
oh I think you got up to all sorts of
trouble when you were my age uh have you
seen my schedule at least statistically
I've wasted less than most mum I know
why you didn't want me to join overwatch
but it's still what I want I didn't want
that life for you but I know that it's
your decision and I will support it mom
don't you think it's time that you told
Sam you're alive you let me worry about
what your father needs to know I always
dreamed of the day we would fight
together wanting a better life for you
with all I ever dreamed of I'd be
watching your back out there furry huh
then I have nothing to worry about
a soldier an alchemist an archer and an
oddity a motley group we have assemble
here just as it has always been you
attract strange companions if we survive
the night this should be our last battle
no I cannot rest until we have justice
the Reaper is a fearsome foe he may
still get the better of us I will get us
home safe as I always do why fight for
this Lord you have never cared much for
the nobility it is true but today we
share a common foe the Reaper it's time
to finish this fight old friend let us
hope we have the strength to see it
through for a man of your years you're
looking pretty good luck well all that
stuff they pumped into me has to be good
for something
what are you going to do in the
Fighting's over Jack I'm a soldier honor
retirement doesn't suit me Jack we're
adults you don't have to sleep outside
I'm fine where I am
seems like neither of us like being dead
very much old soldiers are hard to kill
Anna we all thought you were dead why
didn't you tell me you of all people are
going to ask me that
admit it honor this is better than
retirement
you haven't been took oh I have you you
know I still owe you for saving my life
that one time that one time
you mean Egypt all the time in Russia or
Brazil I feel a lot better having you
watch my back we all need someone we can
trust Jack guess you're going back on my
last Honor what happened to you Gabriel
just like old times right except for the
part where you became a homicidal
murderer I shouldn't be surprised you
took his side you never gave me much
choice why not things may change but you
never do oh how can this be I thought
you were dead
I'm sorry Reinhardt after everything
that happened I needed time Reinhardt I
must say you're looking quite well this
life must agree with you and you are
looking as lovely as ever this is just
like old times Reinhardt the old-timers
must stick together teach these kids a
thing or two what treason brings you to
travel so far from home I was banished
from my home for taking my brother's
life
I can never return you say you do
silence the good doctor Junkin Stein
would profess the same science is a tool
and a method the hand that wields it
decides its course I once met a man who
could summon a dragon as you do
impossible only my clan possesses the
skill my brother could but he is dead
what difference is there between the
witch's magic and your alchemy alchemy
is a science her magic is something
darker I sense that you and the soldier
have history together indeed
and much of it unhappy I can tell you
and the soldier have some history
together
this is not our first battle together
and not the last unless he does
something foolish not sure how I feel
about all this alchemy nonsense
seems like hocus-pocus to me I could
leave you to die if you prefer do you
think that was the last of them
something tells me the worst is yet to
come you do not trust my alchemy do you
all due respect witchcraft and magic
potions are no match for a good six
shooter it's an honor fighting by your
side man oh you always were a charmer we
must stop these abominations created in
the name of science you have your cars
but I'm just looking for a good fire
Jerrod was a fool to love someone like
you you don't know anything about him
you were once a legend but what are you
now just a shell of a woman I take it
you don't want my autograph then honor
they all thought you've ordered well I
had to come back I was worried you'd get
bored not being able to stick your nose
in my business staying out of trouble
Kenji all my best behavior captain you
know Anna there are procedures we could
look into to repair your eye you're very
kind but I'm comfortable with who I am
now it's a good reminder